Well, apparently I've discovered that
I can take these yawn-filled days
And turn them into movies
I've found the secret and trick to it
Under this sky where we don't get along
I closed my heart and locked it
That's how I've managed to live my life
And the melodies now overlap
I wanted a sign, no matter how small
That I could actually find
better than any streetlight
I put a ribbon on each of the
sights that my eyes pick out
And I collect them like souvenirs
as I continue down this path home
The seasons each say hello,
and I shed a few tears as I go
Where should I begin to talk about
this way home that you've given me?
I walk and walk and sometimes
rush on my way to see you
I run and run, wait, no, I should
still walk on my way to see you
Pardon me. May we see
your ID and invitation?
You are now entering the Eden College social gathering venue
This area is highly secured
Ah, Mr. Hamilton.
Please drive through.
The social gathering at Eden College.
A traditional event held every half-term
for Imperial Scholars and their parents,
as well as a handful of the alumni,
including prominent figures
in politics and business,
scholars, engineers, artists, and athletes.
The lineup was always impressive.
The security is rather
intense again this year.
Well, the crowd is filled with VIPs.
I can't help but be a bit nervous knowing
the State Security Service is here.
The level of security here is
the same as a summit meeting.
I was prepared for that, but this
goes beyond even my expectations.
Infiltrating it will prove to be difficult.
The easiest thing would be if I could get
in without needing an Imperial Scholar...
But of course, if things were that simple,
we wouldn't have initiated
Operation Strix to begin with.
In the past, intelligence from the West
tried infiltrating the gathering
many times and ended in failure.
We can't keep failing just so they
can keep strengthening their defenses.
The venue for the event
is the Tower of Wisdom.
Other than the entrance located in front,
there are only a handful of fixed windows.
The roof of the tower is a garden,
but infiltrating from above would draw
too much attention to be feasible.
There are currently no promising
routes from the basement.
At the one and only entrance, they conduct an
extensive identity check and body pat-down.
They also use the most
cutting-edge detectors.
Going in with a disguise or trying to place
a wire on someone would be difficult.
Because none of the surrounding
buildings are taller,
it would be impossible to read lips nearby.
Perhaps there's a way to sneak
into the building days ahead...
No, that would pose quite a risk, too.
So there's no way to infiltrate the venue?
No, with a little bit of force,
it wouldn't be impossible
to infiltrate just once. For example,
if we were trying to assassinate Desmond,
it would have been quite possible.
But the purpose of Operation Strix is
a continuous interaction with Desmond.
To get into his good graces and
extract information from him.
Even if we are able to clear
all of these requirements,
and tried to get close to him
disguised as someone else...
Well, hello again.
Huh? But I didn't attend last time...
Famous people would be easy to trace,
and if they're accompanied by a child,
it'll complicate things even more.
You're being weird today, Papa.
And if I disguise myself
as school staff or a waiter,
I won't even be able to speak with him.
I can't utilize any plans that
could arouse suspicion.
Desmond is extremely cautious, so there's
a possibility he'd never attend again.
My best bet is to interact
with him as Loid Forger.
All I can do right now is make the
necessary preparations for next time.
There'll rarely ever be a chance to
encounter Desmond outside the tower,
but I'll look into any possibilities.
This ends our class for today.
The social gathering is this evening,
so the school will be closed.
Any students who are not attending
should leave immediately.
The social gathering...
I wonder what it's like.
Don't all kinds of celebrities show up?
I heard that the cosmonaut Yachayka
will give a speech.
Ooh, the actress Amy, too.
What? Really?
Hey, is your father going
to be there, too, Damian?
Your older brother is an
Imperial Scholar, after all.
I'm so excited we just have a half-day today.
Hey, are you listening?
This is Damian Desmond from Cecile Hall.
Could you connect me to Demetrius Desmond?
What?
H-Hey, Bro.
What do you want?
Oh, sorry. About tomorrow...
You're going to the social gathering, right?
Yeah.
When you see Father, there's
something I'd like you to ask him.
I was wondering if I could see him,
even just for a little bit, after the gathering.
Can you tell him I'll be waiting
in the courtyard of Library 2?
I'll tell him, but don't get your hopes up.
Father is busy.
Yeah...
Is that all?
Yeah.
All right. Bye.
Hey, let me greet your father.
My father's going to pick me up today.
Then we can both greet him. Okay?
What? No fair. Hey, Damian, let me come, too.
Shut up.
Lord Damian!
Is Second Son planning to meet
with the evil boss today?
Hey, want to go shopping again today?
Anya's plan to use fassun
on Second Son failed.
Which means...
Meeting my papa will lead
to nothing but good things!
Oho.
I'll follow Second Son and
fight the evil boss myself.
What the hell have you been up to all week?!
You're creepy! Stop following me!
Lord Damian, perhaps she...
Wh-What?
Perhaps she's following us to get
in your father's good graces.
Yes! Just like the others!
You stupid uggo!
Stubby-legged uggo!
Well, that's rude.
Don't ever come near me again!
You creepy gorilla-girl stalker!
Anya is thinking of punching him again.
Don't. You'll get expelled.
As I feared, she's still not
getting along with Damian.
So Plan B might be in dire straits, too.
Papa?!
No, perhaps she's trying to make
up with him in her own way.
Well done.
For now, I need to find Damian, who may
encounter his father outside the venue.
Wait! Anya will fight the evil boss, too!
What? Let's go home already.
Are you heading to the meeting spot already?
Your father won't be here until
after the social gathering, right?
That won't be for hours.
So he is meeting with his father. Excellent.
Since we're here, shall we
get closer to the venue?
Wow, it's quite impressive.
Imperial Scholars! I may pee my pants.
Wow, and your father is one of the
top VIPs among all these VIPs.
That goes for you, as well,
since you're his son!
Lord Damian?
I'm not going to see my father after all.
Huh?
What? That's not good!
That's right. My father's amazing. He's very busy.
There's no way he'd have
time to bother with me.
I'll go talk to my bro again.
I'll tell him to cancel the meetup.
That's not happening!
What's your problem?
You're still here, you stalker?
Second Son's scared. Anya can tell.
Huh?!
Wh-What's with her? Is she
actually reading my mind?
A-Anya knows that, um...
That you only got 50 points
on our last language test.
H-How do you know that?!
Wait, that has nothing to do with anything.
I peeked over your shoulder.
Anya's become an actual stalker.
You're scared your father will find
out that you did bad on your test.
Anya totally understands because
she only got 17 points.
Don't lump me in with you!
Anya's a little scared because she's
not sure if Papa loves her or not.
He always gets mad at me.
Anya...
But I believe in him because I love him.
And so...
Anya always shows him her tests,
even if they're real bad.
What were we talking about again?
Dunno.
Damn it!
Lord Damian, where are you going?
This is dumb.
I'm going to wait for
Father in the courtyard.
Lord Damian!
I ain't scared!
I'm not quite sure what happened,
but well done, Anya!
Her provocation worked in my favor!
Huh? You're going to wait, too?
Why?! My car's waiting,
so let's just go home!
Wait... Is she planning to meet his
parents because she hopes to marry him?
She's serious! You must be serious, Anya!
All right, Anya. I'll wait with you!
I will see your resolve through!
Zzz...
I was wrong. She's not serious at all.
Martha! Carry Anya to the car.
We're going home.
As you wish.
Anya's such a free spirit.
Oh, goodbye, sir.
Yes, goodbye.
And then Anya...
Making this replica was the right choice.
Twilight's handmade replica
Cost of materials: 10 dalc
Looks like the gathering
ended without issue.
The security layout...
The flow of people and items, changes...
It was definitely worth it.
All that's left is...
And Desmond's finally here.
He's headed to...
All right.
I wonder if they're about done.
Hmm...
Oh, pardon me, boys.
Did you happen to see a sheep
key chain around here?
It's apparently very
important to my daughter.
But she seems to have
dropped it around here,
so she came to me in tears,
asking me to look for it.
Oh, is this it? It was on
the ground over there.
Oh, that's it! Thank you.
You're a lifesaver.
That's definitely her...
Thank goodness!
Hey, are you Forger's dad, old man?
Hm? Old man?
I am. Oh... are you her classmates?
Wait. I'm sorry if you're not...
But might you be... Damian Desmond?
Y-Yeah, I am.
I'm so terribly sorry!
I'm sorry for what my daughter did
on the day of the entrance ceremony!
Uh, sure...
I wanted to visit your home to apologize,
but I wasn't able to see you or your parents,
so it's been on my mind all this time.
I mean, I live in the dorms.
I'm responsible for my daughter's
rudeness. I'm truly sorry.
Uh, it's fine.
I would still like to
apologize to your parents.
Ah, Lord Damian! Over there! Your father...
I'm truly sorry, Damian.
For the sake of my mission,
I'll be butting into your reunion
with your father for a bit.
Father...
Young Master, who is that man?
Huh? Oh, he's my classmate's father.
U-Um, you must be Chairman Desmond.
Hey, step back. We need you to leave.
It's all right. What is it?
I've been wanting to apologize for my
daughter's rudeness toward your son.
Oh, I haven't properly
introduced myself. I'm...
Loid Forger.
FIRST CONTACT
Council Secretary Byron.
Colonel McNeill of the national army.
Prosecutor Farnham from the Ministry
of Justice. Cosmonaut Yachayka.
And the Chairman of the National
Unity Party, Donovan Desmond.
This social gathering truly is a
gathering of prime intelligence.
Shouldn't we be sending in more
agents to back up Agent Twilight?
Well, would you like to go?
Five minutes after you get in,
you'll be caught in the State
Security Service's net.
Thirty minutes later, you'll be
tortured in their interrogation room.
If we send in inexperienced agents,
we'll just be giving them easy prey.
Don't forget that we're right in
the middle of enemy territory.
Currently, that school...
is the front line of this cold war.
I'm Loid Forger. I'm a doctor who
works at Berlint Central Hospital.
I would like to formally apologize for
my daughter being violent with Damian.
I'm sure it must have been very unpleasant
for Damian and the rest of your family.
Chairman Desmond of
the National Unity Party.
His past quotes found in
newspapers and TV broadcasts,
books he's written...
I've studied everything that might
give me insight into his life.
But it's been impossible to learn anything
about him since he went into hiding.
How can I get closer to him?
Discuss politicians
you've treated
Trade collectibles
Small talk
about current
East-West
affairs
See how he reacts to
anti-Western remarks
Support his
party
Hospital
director info
Try to make him feel guilty
enough to give
in to a demand
An enthusiastic
greeting
Discuss Anya
Discuss Damian
Discuss the children
Start with a heartfelt apology
Discuss the mixer
Mention connections
to the hospital
Mention you're
from the same
province
How can I get him to show
any interest in Loid?
What does he relate to? What enrages him?
I will have to find that
out in this conversation.
And then, eventually,
I will find what's inside him...
and learn all about his plan for war.
I'm truly sorry.
And I would like to visit your
residence to formally apologize.
Ah, so it was you. My staff
informed me about that incident.
I've been so busy that I haven't had
time to address it. Sorry about that.
Father... He was worried about me?
In the next few days,
I will bring you a gift in apology.
Oh, there's no need.
It was merely a squabble between children.
But...
Father! A member of the
Desmond family was punched!
Do you accept that?
Your son is right.
Regardless of the circumstances, it was my
daughter who put her hands on your son.
I vow that I will make it up to you!
It's quite all right. I thank
you for your courtesy, though.
Instant rejection.
You are truly too kind, sir.
Being too persistent will backfire.
If he finds me at all suspicious,
the operation will be ruined.
I need to be careful.
F-Father...
So he really doesn't care about me?
It was humiliating for me.
My face even swelled up!
And yet...
Why? Why can't you get angrier for my sake?
Never mind...
I'm sorry.
No, you have every right to be angry, Damian.
I'll be sure to lecture her properly
so this never happens again.
Then again, my daughter is rather eccentric,
so I'm honestly not sure what to do with her.
Guy's got it rough.
Of course, this is my responsibility,
but I came to the painful realization that
it's impossible to completely control children.
I guess a parent shouldn't assume
they can control their child.
It's not good to have so many
one-sided hopes and disappointments.
Raising a child is truly difficult.
You are correct.
In the end, even the child that
shares your blood is a stranger.
It is simply impossible to understand
what someone else is truly thinking.
People will never be able
to understand each other.
And that's why you're using force to
bring other nations to their knees?
Is that who you really are, Desmond?
You are absolutely right.
I specialize in psychiatry,
but I fear that I may not truly be able to
understand what my patients are feeling.
It's true. "We can talk it out"
is nothing but idealism.
It might be sheer arrogance to think
you can truly understand another.
But...
What's truly important is
to continue walking
beside them despite that.
Candy Coupon
The things my daughter says
and does are truly a mystery to me.
Anya is going to free some candy hostages
at the candy store with this coupon.
Oh, really? Well, do your best.
I decided that I would accept her regardless,
and I try to find every opportunity
I can to talk to her.
Though it doesn't always go well...
I won't abandon this path to obtaining
information and gaining understanding.
I am an intelligence agent, after all.
Didn't you...
also happen to make time for your son,
despite how busy you are?
Hm. You do make a valid point.
I can really see why you
look up to your father.
Anya mentioned it, too.
Huh?
Didn't you recently have an assignment to
explore the career path you're interested in?
Anya was very moved by your report.
It was all she could talk
about when she got home.
All Lies
Really?
Have you seen his presentation, sir?
No.
Oh, that's such a waste!
I only heard it through my daughter,
Actually, he was spying at school
but I still sense just how much he
respects and understands your work.
I was deeply moved.
Your boy is intelligent and
very considerate of you.
Is that so?
I do beg your pardon for saying this,
but I happened to be against the
ideals of the National Unity Party.
And yet, when I heard his report,
I became interested.
It made me realize that you are
genuinely concerned for our country.
I was thinking about attending
one of your lectures next time.
I might be taking this too lightly.
But his report truly was just that wonderful.
That's enough. You can stop, old man.
Sorry.
You are indeed an interesting man.
Forger, was it?
My, what a delightful moment that was.
I guess that's the end.
He knows my name now,
so I'll consider that good enough.
I've memorized his security
team's faces and builds.
I humbly thank you for your time.
Oh, right.
Could you keep the fact that
I talked to you about Anya a secret?
She can be quite the contrarian.
I'm pretty sure she doesn't
actually dislike you.
It'd make me happy if you
could be friends with her.
W-Well, I want to, too...
Huh?
Shut up! Shut up!
Like I have time to waste on that commoner!
Oh, ouch. Well, I'll do my
best to raise our status.
If you'll excuse me.
So, what did you want?
Oh, um...
It's nothing.
What's truly important is
to continue walking
beside them despite that.
If there's nothing else, I'll be going home.
Anya's a little scared because she's
not sure if Papa loves her or not.
But Anya always shows him her tests,
even if they're real bad.
Sir, we should get going.
Father!
I earned a Stella on our midterms!
I-It's only one so far, but I got really
close in the other subjects, too.
Oh... but I got 50 points my
language test the other day.
And...
Also, I got the grand prize
for my griffin sculpture.
Also, um, uh...
I see. Well done.
Father... Why did you come today?
It was just a whim. Don't worry about it.
Damian, continue working hard
so as not to shame the Desmond name.
Yes, sir!
It wasn't much of a conversation,
but I got a decent idea of the
relationship between the Desmonds.
Because the better their relationship,
the better it'll be for Plan B.
Thinking back on Donovan Desmond...
He's indeed elusive.
It might be quicker to
work from the outside in.
I need to take the intel I gained today
back to HQ so we can discuss it.
Stella! Stella!
Stella! Stella! Stella! Stella!
Stella! Stella! Stella! Stella! Stella! Stella!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Loid.
Zzz...
She came home fast asleep for some reason,
and she's been asleep ever since.
Delivery for you.
Papa... Anya's gonna fight the boss, too...
She doesn't seem like
she has a care in the world.
And... I have absolutely no
idea what she's talking about.